<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<movies>
	<movie>
		<User_code>GAB</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>Inside Out</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>[Inside Out] converts complex concepts -- like memory, subconcious, dreams and imagination -- into a visual game, a psychology lesson for both children and adults.</Comments>
		<Genre>93</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>VAL</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>The Revenant</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>The Revenant is among the truly great films of 2015, and is Alejandro Gonzaezel Inarritu&apos;s greatest film... by the end you share in the characters&apos; exhaustion of heart and soul, and perhaps in their glimpse at something infinite, beautiful, and terrifying.</Comments>
		<Genre>93</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>GAB</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>Crimson Peak</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>The story quickly grew predictable and bland, and the design of the ghosts and the role they played in the story left me feeling disappointed.</Comments>
		<Genre>93</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>VAL</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>In The Heart of the Sea</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>Warner Bros. would have been better off sticking with the film&apos;s original March release date and selling it as a horror movie.</Comments>
		<Genre>93</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>GAB</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>The Man from Uncle</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>The re-invention might have been better as straight-up thriller. More story and less comedy fails would have helped.</Comments>
		<Genre>93</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code></User_code>
		<Movie_Name></Movie_Name>
		<Comments></Comments>
		<Genre></Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>gabriel</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>111</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>true</Comments>
		<Genre>some folm</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>V</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>A</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>L</Comments>
		<Genre>I</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>Valeriu </User_code>
		<Movie_Name>Computer science </Movie_Name>
		<Comments>Doing a course at National College of Ireland it&apos;s has been a excellent decision based on the teacher&apos;s and facilities around college. </Comments>
		<Genre>2</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>Janie Henderson</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>General</Movie_Name>
		<Comments>NCI is a great college, I studied here part-time and it was very handy to get to class after work as it&apos;s right in the centre of Dublin, I just hopped on the LUAS. Love the area, nice and buzzy and loads of places nearby to grab food or a coffee too. Everyone in my class got on great, shared notes and study tips and made good friends. Lecturers were v good, notes always available online and felt like they were always available over email or phone or for a chat after class.</Comments>
		<Genre>5</Genre>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<User_code>Annie Japaud</User_code>
		<Movie_Name>Web Development </Movie_Name>
		<Comments>I took a 6 month intensive online course in Web Development and it was a fantastic experience. Our teacher Sam was absolutely great and I passed and graduated thanks to him. I met some friends I still keep in touch with and I would go black for more if I could.</Comments>
		<Genre>5</Genre>
	</movie>
</movies>